mojofiti.com 2012-01-29

# Mojofiti™ — Blog

Effective Date: February 24, 2010

Mojofiti’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect personal information, and how we use and disclose any such personal information. “Personal information,” as used in this Privacy Policy, is information that allows a person to directly identify another individual.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to Mojofiti’s Terms of Service. By using our site, you expressly consent to the processing of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. “Processing” means using cookies on a computer or deleting, using, combining or disclosing information, all of which will take place in the United States. If you reside in the European Union or any other country outside the United States, your personal information will be transferred to the United States, and processed and stored under United States privacy standards. By visiting our site, you consent to such transfer and processing in the United States.

**Although Mojofiti provides machine translations of all of its terms, guidelines and additional terms into multiple languages on www.mojofiti.com, occasionally inaccuracies exist in these machine translated terms, guidelines and additional terms. The English versions of the Mojofiti Privacy Policy, Mojofiti Terms of Use, Mojofiti Safety Tips, and any additional terms posted on the site will serve as the official version of these policies and terms, and shall govern in the case of any discrepancy between the policies and terms that arises as a result of inaccuracies resulting from such machine translation.**

## How the Mojofiti Platform Operates

Mojofiti provides an online platform that enables a registered User to communicate with other Users through the posting of photographs and personal information (“user content”). Additionally, the Mojofiti Platform incorporates the use of translation technology and actual human translators to enable Mojofiti Users worldwide to make postings that can be read by other Mojofiti Users in spite of linguistic barriers.

While we make a good faith effort to provide accurate translations of all user content, this is not always possible. When you use our service, you should be aware that inaccuracies, defects and errors occasionally exist in the translations provided by the translation technology and Mojolingual Premium Translation Services employed on our Site. As stated in our Terms of Service, all translations are provided on an “AS IS” and “WITH ALL FAULTS” basis. Mojofiti does not intentionally misrepresent any user content, and shall not be held responsible for any inaccurate translations published on the Mojofiti Platform.

## The Information We Collect

Our primary goals in collecting your personal information are to provide you with the services made available through our site, to enable us to communicate with you, and to enable you to manage your registered user account.

When you visit Mojofiti, you provide us with two types of information: personal information that you knowingly disclose to us and web site use information that we collect as you interact with our website. First, when you register with Mojofiti, you provide us with personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, your birthday and any other personal or preference information that you provide us with. We also collect passive data when you visit our site such as your browser type, your IP address, and aggregate user data.

Additionally, we store certain information from your browser using cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a User’s computer tied to information about the User. We use cookies to identify a User’s internet browser and store the User’s preferences. Data in cookies may also be used to authenticate user sessions or provide services. A session cookie enables certain features of our site and service and is deleted from your computer when you leave the site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. You can also instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from a website.

## How We Use Your Personal Information

Mojofiti is a service that allows you to share information with friends and other network members worldwide. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission, or engage in the sale of email addresses or any other personal information. We share your information with third parties only when we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer our service, when it is legally required, or when it is permitted by you.

We may use your personal information to operate, provide, improve and maintain the Mojofiti Platform, and our other services and systems, and to develop new products and services; to personalize and display advertisements via our own advertising engine or server and other content on the Mojofiti Platform; to create aggregate data regarding Users’ taste preferences for use by third party advertisers; to prevent abusive and fraudulent use of the Mojofiti Platform; to send you administrative messages and information about social networks, content, and Mojofiti services in which you may be interested; and for other administrative and internal business purposes.

Mojofiti may provide your personal information to third party advertisers or trusted third party service providers who help us facilitate some of the regular features and Premium Services we offer, including our Premium Translation Services. We share your personal information with these third parties only to the extent necessary, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring that such third parties maintain the privacy and security of your data.

Finally, we will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish and exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information that we believe is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of Mojofiti’s Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by Applicable Law.

## Links to Other Websites

Mojofiti services may be linked to internet sites operated by other companies. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization, or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. Mojofiti is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with Mojofiti services. Once you leave Mojofiti via a link or by accessing a third party application such as a widget, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party to determine how they will handle any personal information they receive from you.

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Mojofiti are sometimes delivered directly to Users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies on to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and “web beacons” or “1×1 gifs” to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Mojofiti does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your content within Mojofiti unless you choose to share it with them.

The Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Mojofiti but does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking devices by any of its advertisers.

## Security

Mojofiti Users should be aware that they post user content at their own risk. Mojofiti uses industry standard security measures to protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of Mojofiti members’ personal information. In doing so, we make good faith efforts to maintain the security of all personal information gathered from Users. However, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent “hackers” or other unauthorized persons from illegally accessing or obtaining this information, or from perpetuating identity theft.

Additionally, we are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the site. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Mojofiti is a violation of the Mojofiti Terms of Service and should be reported by clicking on the “report abuse” link found on any Mojifitian’s page of our Site.

## Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on Mojofiti is available through the “my account” menu. Mojofiti Users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. The information will be deleted immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their account may do so using the “delete account” function under the “settings” tab of the “my account” menu.

## Change of Ownership/Affiliates

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets, to another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your personal information, including your email address, to that entity. Mojofiti will use reasonable efforts to notify registered Users of such a transfer, such as through notification by email or posting information on our homepage, at our discretion.

Although Mojofiti does not currently have a parent company or any subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that it controls or is under common control with (collectively, “affiliates”), it may in the future. Mojofiti may share some or all of your personal information with its affiliates, in which case we will seek to require that those affiliates honor this Privacy Policy.

## Children

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children less than thirteen years of age. Mojofiti does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of thirteen or allow such persons to register. If you are under thirteen years of age, please do not attempt to register on our website. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information, he or she should contact us using the “report abuse” link found on any Mojofitian’s page of our site to have the child’s account deleted. If we become aware that a child under the age of thirteen has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

## Terms of Service, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Mojofiti, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service and all its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages, and choice of law. We reserve the right to make changes in our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service at any time. We will notify you of any material changes in our Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our site, and indicating the new policy’s effective date. Continued use of our site following such notice shall indicate your acknowledgement of the changes, and your agreement to be bound by the revised terms and conditions contained in the new Privacy Policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us via electronic or regular mail:

**  
Mojofiti.com  
Attn: Community Manager  
1225 17th Street, Suite 3030  
Denver, CO 80202  
**
